<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
				<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
					<title>Moluko Store</title>
					<link rel="self" href="http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com"/>
					<updated>2010-03-10T17:25:50Z</updated>
					<author>
						<name>Moluko Store</name>
					</author>
					<id>tag:1268241950</id>
				<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[MacBook]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/MacBook.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Redesigned with a precision unibody enclosure crafted from a single block of aluminum, the MacBook is thinner and lighter than its predecessor as well as stronger and more durable. But Apple didn&#039;t stop innovating with the body&#039;s design. The MacBook also includes a new 13.3-inch, LED-backlit glass display (instead of an LCD panel) and a glass trackpad that doesn&#039;t include a button (for larger tracking area) and features includes Apple&#039;s Multi-Touch technology.LED-backlit display.The ultrathin 1280-by-800-pixel LED-backlit display shows off your digital media perfectly. And it&#039;s as easy on the environment as it is on the eyes: The gorgeous glass and aluminum enclosure is arsenic- and mercury-free, and LED technology makes it more power efficient.Advanced NVIDIA integrated graphics.Experience the most powerful MacBook graphics ever. With a new NVIDIA GeForce 9400M processor, the new MacBook delivers up to 5x more graphics performance, so you can immerse yourself in lifelike 3D games.M...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shop Mac]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[5]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[1299.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/u/874/macbook__58678_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[4.50 lbs]]></g:weight>
	<g:height><![CDATA[0.9000 inches]]></g:height>
	<g:length><![CDATA[8.9400 inches]]></g:length>
	<g:width><![CDATA[12.7800 inches]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[MacBook Pro]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/MacBook-Pro.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Redesigned with a precision unibody enclosure crafted from a single block of aluminum, the MacBook Pro is thinner and lighter than its predecessor as well as stronger and more durable. But Apple didn&#039;t stop innovating with the body&#039;s design. The MacBook Pro also includes a new 15-inch, LED-backlit glass display (instead of an LCD panel) and a glass trackpad that doesn&#039;t include a button (for larger tracking area) and features includes Apple&#039;s Multi-Touch technology.LED-backlit widescreen display.Seamless glass and instant full screen brightness make your brilliant ideas flat-out spectacular. The 17-inch model goes further, offering a high-resolution display with a 60 percent greater color gamut.Smooth glass Multi-Touch trackpad.Now the entire trackpad is also the button, so it&#039;s clickable everywhere. And it offers even more Multi-Touch gestures and functionality.High-performance NVIDIA graphics.MacBook Pro features two NVIDIA graphics processors &amp;#8212; one discrete and one integrat...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shop Mac]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[6]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[1999.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/b/384/mbp1__28249_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[5.50 lbs]]></g:weight>
	<g:height><![CDATA[0.9500 inches]]></g:height>
	<g:length><![CDATA[9.8200 inches]]></g:length>
	<g:width><![CDATA[14.3500 inches]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[MacBook Air]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/MacBook-Air.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[With the MacBook Air, Apple has created the world&#039;s thinnest laptop--measuring an unprecedented 0.16-inches at its thinnest point (and 0.76 inches thick overall). Apple brings its vaunted multi-touch technology, found on the iPhone, to its laptops with the MacBook Air, enabling you to pinch, swipe, or rotate to zoom in on text, advance through a photo album, or adjust an image via the oversized trackpad. And the MacBook Air embodies Apple&#039;s continuing environmental progress with its aluminum enclosure, a material highly desired by recyclers; Apple&#039;s first mercury-free LCD display with arsenic-free glass; and brominated flame retardant-free material for the majority of circuit boards as well as PVC-free internal cables.Flat-out stunningFrom 0.16 to 0.76 inch thin and weighing only 3.0 pounds, MacBook Air sets new standards for ultraportable computing &amp;#8212; without the usual ultraportable compromises.Faster Intel mobile architectureWith speeds up to 1.86GHz, the Intel Core 2 Duo pro...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shop Mac]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[7]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[1799.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/e/363/mba1__68974_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[3.00 lbs]]></g:weight>
	<g:height><![CDATA[0.7600 inches]]></g:height>
	<g:length><![CDATA[8.9400 inches]]></g:length>
	<g:width><![CDATA[12.8000 inches]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Mac Pro]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Mac-Pro.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Boost your productivity with the Apple Mac Pro desktop PC - the fastest Mac Apple has ever made. Combining two of Intel&#039;s new 64-bit, 45-nanometer Quad-Core Xeon 5400 processors running at 2.8 GHz, the Mac Pro is an unbelievably powerful workstation that can handle even the most intensive graphics rendering.8 cores, standard.8-core processing was once reserved as a high-end option. Now it&#039;s at the heart of the Mac Pro line. This incredible power stems from all-new Quad-Core Intel Xeon &amp;#8220;Harpertown&amp;#8221; processors, featuring speeds up to 3.2GHz and 12MB of L2 cache per processor.Blazing fast, up to 2x performance.With its 8-core processing, advanced Xeon architecture, 1600MHz dual independent front-side buses, and 800MHz memory, the new Mac Pro delivers up to 2x greater application performance.2Up to 4TB storage, RAID, and SAS.The cable-free, direct-attach hard drive bays make it easy to install up to 4TB of storage with Serial ATA 3Gb/s drives. For enhanced data protection, t...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shop Mac]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[28]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[2799.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/x/927/picture_1__76974_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[MAC-PRO]]></g:model_number>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[53.80 lbs]]></g:weight>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[iPod Shuffle]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/iPod-Shuffle.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The world&amp;#8217;s smallest digital music player, the 1GB iPod shuffle lets you wear up to 500 songs on your sleeve. Or your lapel. Or your belt. Clip on iPod shuffle and wear it as a badge of musical devotion.Instant attachment.Clip on the world&amp;#8217;s most wearable music player and take up to 500 songs with you anywhere. Choose from two capacities and five colors &amp;#8212; including four new hues &amp;#8212; to make your musical fashion statement.Random meets rhythm.Mix up your music with a flip of the shuffle switch. Flip it again to play your handpicked playlists and albums in the order you synced them with iTunes.Everything is easy.Charge and sync with the included USB dock. Operate the iPod shuffle controls with one hand. Enjoy up to 12 hours straight of skip-free music playback.Technical DetailsStore up to 500 songsStores data via USB flash driveSkip-free audio playbackUp to 12 hours playtime when fully chargedCharging via included USB dockAutofill from your entire music library fo...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shop iPod]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[1]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[49.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/c/587/shuffle_silver__41436_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[0.03 lbs]]></g:weight>
	<g:height><![CDATA[1.0700 inches]]></g:height>
	<g:length><![CDATA[0.4100 inches]]></g:length>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.6200 inches]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[iPod Nano]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/iPod-Nano.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Colour isn&#039;t the only brilliant new iPod Nano feature. For those about to rock, we give you nine amazing colours. But that&amp;#8217;s only part of the story. Feel the curved, all-aluminum and glass design and you won&amp;#8217;t want to put iPod nano down. The accelerometer comes to iPod nano. Give it a shake to shuffle your music. Turn it sideways to view Cover Flow. And play games designed with your moves in mind.Meet a musical Genius.With just a few clicks, the new Genius feature finds the songs on your iPod nano that go great together and makes a Genius Playlist for you.Rock and roll over.Thanks to the built-in accelerometer, you can rotate iPod nano to flip through album art with Cover Flow. Watch movies and TV shows in widescreen. And view photos in either portrait or landscape.Shake to shuffle.Just give iPod nano a shake and it shuffles to a different song in your music library.Curved ahead of the curve.iPod nano now comes in nine vibrant colors and a new curved aluminum and glass d...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shop iPod]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[2]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[149.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/k/439/nano_black__52123_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[0.08 lbs]]></g:weight>
	<g:height><![CDATA[3.6000 inches]]></g:height>
	<g:length><![CDATA[0.2400 inches]]></g:length>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.5000 inches]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[iPod Classic]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/iPod-Classic.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[With 120GB of storage, iPod classic can hold up to 30,000 songs, 150 hours of video, or 25,000 photos. That&amp;#8217;s more than enough room for a day&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8212; or a lifetime&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8212; worth of entertainment. Available in quintessential silver or striking new black, iPod classic catches your eye with its sleek, all-metal enclosure composed of anodised aluminium and polished stainless steel.Classic beauty.Beautiful, durable, and sleek, iPod classic features an anodized aluminum and polished stainless steel enclosure with rounded edges. Choose quintessential silver or striking new black.A Genius in the house.With just a few clicks, the new Genius feature creates a playlist of tracks in your library that go great together.Enjoy the view.With Cover Flow, you can browse through your music collection by flipping through album art. Select an album to turn it over and see the track list.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shop iPod]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[3]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[249.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/d/271/product_white_classic__86995_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[249.00 lbs]]></g:weight>
	<g:height><![CDATA[4.1000 inches]]></g:height>
	<g:length><![CDATA[0.4100 inches]]></g:length>
	<g:width><![CDATA[2.4000 inches]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[iPod Touch]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/iPod-Touch.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[With a stunningly thin, contoured stainless steel design, iPod touch feels even better in your hand. And the new volume buttons and built-in speaker give you more to love. Groundbreaking technologies built into iPod touch &amp;#8212; such as the Multi-Touch display, accelerometer, and 3D graphics &amp;#8212; immerse you in the action. The new Genius feature turns iPod touch into a highly intelligent, personal DJ. With a few taps, it creates a playlist by finding songs in your library that go great together.Get your mobile game on.With a built-in speaker and groundbreaking technologies such as the Multi-Touch display, accelerometer, and 3D graphics, iPod touch puts an amazing gaming experience in the palm of your hand.Rock &#039;n&#039; run with Nike+.iPod touch now includes built-in Nike + iPod support. Just slip the Nike + iPod Sensor (available separately) into your Nike+ shoe and start your run. The sensor communicates wirelessly with your iPod touch, tracking your time, distance, and calories bur...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shop iPod]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[4]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[229.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/g/956/touch1__14678_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[0.25 lbs]]></g:weight>
	<g:height><![CDATA[4.1000 inches]]></g:height>
	<g:length><![CDATA[0.3000 inches]]></g:length>
	<g:width><![CDATA[2.4000 inches]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Apple Mighty Mouse]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Apple-Mighty-Mouse.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[It&#039;s the wired mouse that reinvents the wheel &amp;mdash; the scroll wheel. Mighty Mouse features the amazing Scroll Ball that lets you move anywhere inside a document, literally without lifting a finger. And with touch-sensitive technology concealed under the seamless top shell, you can choose either the versatility of a four-button mouse or the simplicity of a single-button beauty.Innovative Scroll Ball and buttonPerfectly positioned to roll smoothly under just one finger, Mighty Mouse&#039;s Scroll Ball offers full 360-degree scrolling capability &amp;#8212; up/down, left/right and diagonally. You can scroll long web pages, pan full-size images, maneuver around large spreadsheets, control a video timeline and more. And you can even click the Scroll Ball to access your favorite Tiger features such as Dashboard, Spotlight or Expos&amp;eacute;.Touch-sensitive top shellIt looks and feels like a sleek one-button mouse, but Mighty Mouse&#039;s smooth top shell hides a powerful secret: touch-sensitive techno...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[14]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[69.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/z/115/mighty__34349_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[MIGHTYMOUSE]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Apple Wireless Mighty Mouse]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Apple-Wireless-Mighty-Mouse.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Now you can get the world-famous Mighty Mouse without the tail. With its Bluetooth technology, the wireless Mighty Mouse gives you complete freedom of movement with no cable clutter. It features the popular Scroll Ball that lets you move anywhere inside a document, without lifting a finger. And its laser tracking technology allows it to work on more surfaces with greater precision.Bluetooth technology, ultimate portabilityWith its secure, reliable Bluetooth technology, wireless Mighty Mouse goes wherever you do. Pair it with any Bluetooth-enabled Mac to work untethered and uncluttered at your desk or on the go, and it operates with either one or two AA batteries &amp;#8212; no bulky dock required.Laser tracking engineThe wireless Mighty Mouse features a laser tracking engine that&#039;s up to 20 times more sensitive to surface details than traditional optical technology. That means it can track with precision on more surfaces than ever &amp;#8212; even smooth or polished surfaces &amp;#8212; with no...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[15]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[99.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/q/839/wirelessm__39624_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[WIRELESS-MIGHTY]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Logitech VX Nano Cordless Laser Mouse]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Logitech-VX-Nano-Cordless-Laser-Mouse.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Simplify life on the road with the Logitech VX Nano Cordless Laser Mouse. It&#039;s always ready for use, thanks to one of the world&#039;s smallest USB receivers. Plug it into your notebook&#039;s USB port just once, then forget about it. No more broken or lost receivers and no more hassles.FeaturesPlug-and-forget nano-receiver that&#039;s barely larger than a coinRobust wireless connection with advanced 2.4 GHz cordless technologyAlways ready, since you can leave the nano-receiver plugged into your notebook all the timeStylish pouch to protect your mouse when it&#039;s not in useLonger battery life--up to 6 months of use (or longer with the convenient on/off switch)Slim, ultra-portable mouse design that slips easily into your notebook bagStorable receiver fits inside the mouse when you need to free up a USB port; shuts down when stored to save battery lifeHyper-fast scrolling with the nearly frictionless scroll wheelForward/backward buttons for effortless Internet navigationFive programmable buttons for c...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[16]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[69.9600]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Logitech]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/n/957/loginano__47715_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[LOGITECH-NANO]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Apple Wireless Keyboard]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Apple-Wireless-Keyboard.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Apple Wireless Keyboard has been completely redesigned, inside and out. It features an elegant, ultra-thin anodized aluminum enclosure with low-profile keys that provide crisp, responsive feel. It also has function keys for one-touch access to a variety of Mac features such as screen brightness, volume, eject, play/pause, fast-forward and rewind, Expose, and Dashboard. Its compact design fits on your lap or on even the most crowded desk. And its Bluetooth wireless technology lets you use it just about anywhere within 30 feet of your Mac.The keyboard automatically powers down when you&#039;re not using it and turns on instantly as soon as you start typing. This intelligent power management means you&#039;ll get up to nine months of battery life based on average usage patterns. It also has an on/off switch for when you&#039;re away from your computer for a long time.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[17]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[79.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/s/441/wireless_1_20070813new__23539_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[WIRELESS-KEYBOARD]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Crumpler Considerable Embarrassment Bag]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Crumpler-Considerable-Embarrassment-Bag.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[With a roomy unpadded cargo compartment and a padded sleeve that accommodates MacBook or 15-inch MacBook Pro notebooks, the Crumpler Considerable Embarrassment gives you the best of both worlds.FeaturesPadded notebook compartment with six-pocket organizerExternal zip pocketThree internal front pocketsAdjustable shoulder strap with padClip and velcro release flapFits 15-in. MacBook Pro and 13-in. MacBook models]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Notebook Cases]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[18]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[89.9500]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Crumpler]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/m/973/crumpler1__71917_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[CRUMPLER-EMB]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Higher Ground Shuttle for 13-inch Notebooks]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Higher-Ground-Shuttle-for-13%252dinch-Notebooks.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Small in size and big on protection, the Higher Ground Shuttle lets you use your notebook while it&#039;s still in the case--for the ultimate in convenience. For the most in comfort, the Shuttle&#039;s cooldeck provides non-slip riser pads that facilitate airflow so your lap and your computer stay cooler. And if you&#039;d like the freedom of carrying the Shuttle on your back, you can get the optional lightweight mesh backpack strap attachment--in addition to the single shoulder strap that&#039;s included. Features Full-time protection since your notebook never has to leave its caseCooldeck for computer heat dissipationSingle shoulder strap (backpack option available)Convenient for use on your lap or desktop surfaceRigid frame and shock-absorbing foam padding throughoutReinforcement at all stress pointsConstructed of the finest expedition grade fabricsHeavy waterproof coating on all fabricsShields your lap from excessive heat buildup]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Notebook Cases]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[19]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[39.9500]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Higher Ground]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/y/211/higher__56943_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Speck 13-inch SeeThru Satin Case]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Speck-13%252dinch-SeeThru-Satin-Case.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Give your aluminum MacBook a smooth yet easily gripped semi-translucent frosted finish that effortlessly slips in and out of your bag. The SeeThru Satin case also ensures access to all your important plugs and drives while protecting your precious investment.FeaturesSilky-smooth soft-touch hard shell protectionProtection from scrapes and scratchesSmooth yet grippy rubberized exterior textureEnsures full range of motion for MacBook displayFull venting for safe heat disbursementAccess to all ports, battery check button, and CD/DVD driveEasy installation and removalBuilt-in rubberized feet for stability on flat surfacesSoft cleaning clothFits the aluminum 13-inch MacBook]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Notebook Cases]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[20]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[49.9500]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Speck]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/s/692/speck__69277_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[SPEC-13-B]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[booq Mamba Saddle]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/booq-Mamba-Saddle.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[With its boldly-colored interior and elegant exterior, its zippered accessory pouch for small items, and its impeccable finish and convenient pocket layout, the Mamba Saddle is the ideal bag for your life and your life at work.The Mamba Saddle also includes booq&#039;s Terralinq service, which may help reunite you with your bag if it&#039;s ever lost. To make this possible, each booq bag carries a unique item number on a metal label. When you register that number it creates a link with your identity. Then if your bag is reported as lost and found, Terralinq will attempt to contact you with its location and the finder&#039;s contact information.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Notebook Cases]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[21]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[124.9500]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[booq]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/e/629/booq__29431_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[BOOQ-MAMBO]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Elgato EyeTV DTT Deluxe]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Elgato-EyeTV-DTT-Deluxe.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[EyeTV DTT Deluxe is an extraordinarily powerful miniature TV tuner that delivers digital terrestrial television (DVB-T, also known as DTT or Freeview) to your Mac. Exceptionally small and beautifully designed, EyeTV DTT Deluxe slips easily into the USB port of any Mac without blocking other devices. EyeTV DTT Deluxe comes with an EyeTV Remote and offers a variety of options for aerial reception. These options vary from a miniature telescopic aerial, a portable rod aerial with a tilt/swivel magnetic base and detachable suction cup, and an adapter to connect EyeTV DTT Deluxe to a rooftop aerial if necessary.FeaturesReceives digital TV (DVB-T, or Freeview)Miniature USB stick; does not cover any other ports, even on a MacBook AirTwo types of aerial included plus unique IEC-MCX adapter cableComes with an EyeTV RemoteSuperb Television ReceptionDespite its extraordinary size, EyeTV DTT Deluxe is a powerful TV tuner that delivers full-size, crystal-clear reception and uncompromising quality...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Video Devices]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[8]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[199.9500]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Elgato]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/y/179/eyetvdtt__28577_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Elgato EyeTV 250 Plus Digital TV Recorder]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Elgato-EyeTV-250-Plus-Digital-TV-Recorder.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[EyeTV 250 Plus is a hybrid TV tuner for the Mac with a powerful hardware encoder for higher-quality recordings and smaller- sized video files. EyeTV 250 Plus receives both free over-the-air HDTV as well as analog TV, and offers a complete solution for moving your video collection from VHS tape to DVD-Video. Watch live TV on your MacPause the TV show while you get a snack, rewind and watch that great play again, or fast forward past the advertisements. Scale the TV window down so you can watch TV while you surf the web, or go &quot;Full Screen&quot; and channel surf from the couch using an EyeTV or Apple Remote. Organize channelsEyeTV provides detailed information about each television channel. Drag and drop the ones you watch most frequently into a &quot;favorites&quot; list, or go a step further and organize your sports, news, or movie channels into their own lists. Record your favorite showsHit the record button now or cruise through the Program Guide and pick the shows you want to record up to two w...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Video Devices]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[9]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[429.9500]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Elgato]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/u/925/eye250__72298_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Logitech Pure-Fi Anywhere Speakers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Logitech-Pure%252dFi-Anywhere-Speakers.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Pure-Fi Anywhere speaker system uses a unique combination of speaker drivers to deliver clear sound with maximum bass and minimal distortion. Its compact size and long battery life make it the ideal companion to your iPod or iPhone.FeaturesAdvanced acoustics for exceptionally clear soundThree-inch pressure drivers to maximize bass responseStereXL technology widens the stereo image dramaticallyTen-hour rechargeable battery for longer listeningBattery-level indicator eliminates surprisesTravel case to protect and store speakers.iPhone or iPod charged whenever it&#039;s dockedWireless remote to control your iPod or iPhone and browse content]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[22]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[129.9500]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Logitech]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/v/144/logitechpure__47956_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[PUREFI]]></g:model_number>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.60 lbs]]></g:weight>
	<g:height><![CDATA[3.6000 inches]]></g:height>
	<g:length><![CDATA[1.5000 inches]]></g:length>
	<g:width><![CDATA[13.2000 inches]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Apple In-Ear Headphones with Remote and Mic]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Apple-In%252dEar-Headphones-with-Remote-and-Mic.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Hear every detail of your music every time you tune in with the Apple In-Ear Headphones with Remote and Mic. They offer pro audio performance and impressive sound isolation, and convenient buttons let you adjust the volume and control music and video playback.Rediscover your music.Put on the Apple In-Ear Headphones, select your favorite track, and hear musical details you never knew existed. It&#039;s almost like you&#039;re experiencing your music for the first time.Technical SpecificationsFrequency response: 5Hz to 21kHzImpedance (at 100Hz): 23 ohmsSensitivity (at 100Hz): 109 dB SPL/mWDrivers: Custom two-way balanced armature (woofer and tweeter in each earpiece)]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[23]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[79.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/h/732/earphones1__37199_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[APPLE-INEAR]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Speck PixelSkin Case for iPhone 3G]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Speck-PixelSkin-Case-for-iPhone-3G.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Fun color and soft, tiled textures make the Speck PixelSkin case the ideal way to protect your iPhone 3G. This durable, rubberized case helps you keep your grip on your iPhone and fully protects against bumps and scrapes without adding bulk. Plus, PixelSkin layers on style and not frustration with complete access to all ports and controls while cased.FeaturesSoft matte-finish provides comfort and extra gripTiled textured surfaces enhance contrast and add characterLightweight, durable design protects without adding bulkFront raised ridges recess your screen to protect it when placed face downComplete access to all ports, controls, and sensors while cased]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[26]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[24.9500]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Speck]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/x/056/speckpi__17982_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[SPECK-IPHONE]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Apple iPhone Bluetooth Headset]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Apple-iPhone-Bluetooth-Headset.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Enjoy wireless convenience and crystal-clear audio when talking on your iPhone. The iPhone Bluetooth Headset features a single button that lets you make and receive phone calls simply and intuitively. And the innovative design is sure to turn a few heads.FeaturesUp to 5.5 hours of talk time; up to 72 hours of standby time*Lightweight earpiece for a secure, comfortable fit in left or right earConvenient autopairing with iPhoneStylish anodized aluminum casing]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[27]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[99.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/o/784/bluetooth__97348_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[APPLE-BLUE]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Logitech Pure-Fi Anywhere Speakers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Logitech-Pure%252dFi-Anywhere-Speakers.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Pure-Fi Anywhere speaker system uses a unique combination of speaker drivers to deliver clear sound with maximum bass and minimal distortion. Its compact size and long battery life make it the ideal companion to your iPod or iPhone.FeaturesAdvanced acoustics for exceptionally clear soundThree-inch pressure drivers to maximize bass responseStereXL technology widens the stereo image dramaticallyTen-hour rechargeable battery for longer listeningBattery-level indicator eliminates surprisesTravel case to protect and store speakers.iPhone or iPod charged whenever it&#039;s dockedWireless remote to control your iPod or iPhone and browse content]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[22]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[129.9500]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Logitech]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/v/144/logitechpure__47956_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[PUREFI]]></g:model_number>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.60 lbs]]></g:weight>
	<g:height><![CDATA[3.6000 inches]]></g:height>
	<g:length><![CDATA[1.5000 inches]]></g:length>
	<g:width><![CDATA[13.2000 inches]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Apple In-Ear Headphones with Remote and Mic]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Apple-In%252dEar-Headphones-with-Remote-and-Mic.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Hear every detail of your music every time you tune in with the Apple In-Ear Headphones with Remote and Mic. They offer pro audio performance and impressive sound isolation, and convenient buttons let you adjust the volume and control music and video playback.Rediscover your music.Put on the Apple In-Ear Headphones, select your favorite track, and hear musical details you never knew existed. It&#039;s almost like you&#039;re experiencing your music for the first time.Technical SpecificationsFrequency response: 5Hz to 21kHzImpedance (at 100Hz): 23 ohmsSensitivity (at 100Hz): 109 dB SPL/mWDrivers: Custom two-way balanced armature (woofer and tweeter in each earpiece)]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[23]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[79.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/h/732/earphones1__37199_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[APPLE-INEAR]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Apple iPod Socks]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Apple-iPod-Socks.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[So add a dash of color to your iPod with iPod Socks, the year&#039;s coziest and most vibrant iPod accessory.It doesn&#039;t matter which iPod model you have because iPod Socks fit all of them. And it doesn&#039;t matter what your mood is because each iPod Socks package includes six bright colors so you can pick the one that feels best.Forgive us if we&#039;re stating the obvious, but here&#039;s how it works: Just slide your iPod into the sock to keep it safe and warm. Slide it out to dock or change playlists. It&#039;s as easy as... putting on a pair of socks.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[24]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[29.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/b/466/ipodsocks__32739_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[IPOD-SOCKS]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Incase Sports Armband for iPod Nano]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Incase-Sports-Armband-for-iPod-Nano.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Constructed out of lightweight, washable neoprene and reflective materials, the adjustable Incase Sports Armband is the functional and secure way to carry your iPod nano during your run or workout. The heavy-duty velcro adjustment provides for a universal fit while the clear cover allows convenient access to widescreen and touch controls.FeaturesComplete protection for iPod nano Form-fitting, washable neoprene construction Reflective material for enhanced visibilityVelcro adjustment for universal fitEasy access to headphone jack, hold switch, and dock connectorCustom fit for iPod nano (4th. Gen.)]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[25]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[29.9500]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Incase]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/l/464/incase__24242_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[INCASE-NANO]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Office for Mac 2008 - Home and Student]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Office-for-Mac-2008-%252d-Home-and-Student.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your presentation will make an impact. Your documents will be professional. Your analysis will be insightful. And Office 2008 will be there.The latest version of the industry standard for productivity software on the Macintosh platform. Microsoft&amp;reg; Office 2008 for Mac is more powerful and easier to use. Office 2008 combines Microsoft Word for Mac, Microsoft Power-Point&amp;reg; for Mac, Microsoft Excel&amp;reg; for Mac, Microsoft Entourage&amp;reg; for Mac, and Microsoft Messenger for Mac and lets you easily create high-impact documents and seamlessly share your ideas with others, whether they are on the Mac or Windows&amp;reg; platform.Word 2008Powerful new tools, more than 100 designer templates, rich themes, and an intuitive user interface will help you make your ideas look as good as they are.Excel 2008It&#039;s a numbers game. With Excel 2008, analyze, share, and manage your data, and easily create persuasive charts and thought-provoking graphs for powerful results.PowerPoint 2008Your presentati...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Software]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[10]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[229.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/z/955/office_student__53504_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[OFFICE08-H&amp;S]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Office 2008 for Mac - Special Media Edition]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/Office-2008-for-Mac-%252d-Special-Media-Edition.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Your presentation will make an impact. Your documents will be professional. Your analysis will be insightful. And Office 2008 will be there.The latest version of the industry standard for productivity software on the Macintosh platform. Microsoft&amp;reg; Office 2008 for Mac is more powerful and easier to use. Office 2008 combines Microsoft Word for Mac, Microsoft Power-Point&amp;reg; for Mac, Microsoft Excel&amp;reg; for Mac, Microsoft Entourage&amp;reg; for Mac, and Microsoft Messenger for Mac and lets you easily create high-impact documents and seamlessly share your ideas with others, whether they are on the Mac or Windows&amp;reg; platform.Microsoft Expression MediaDrag-and-drop digital asset management, batch conversion and tagging, even built-in archiving and backup capabilities help you manage more than 100,000 files and hundreds of format types across multiple storage devices.Word 2008Powerful new tools, more than 100 designer templates, rich themes, and an intuitive user interface will help yo...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Software]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[11]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[499.9500]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/f/353/office_media__57778_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[iWork 09]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/iWork-09.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[iWork, Apple&#039;s productivity suite, is the easiest way to create great-looking documents, spreadsheets, and presentations. Writing and page layout are easy using Pages. Numbers gives you simple ways to make sense of your data. New cinematic animations, transitions, and effects in Keynote will keep your audience captivated. And iWork is compatible with Microsoft Office, so sharing your work is even easier.Compatibility and SharingiWork &#039;09 makes it easy to exchange documents with anyone.Open Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint files in iWork.Save your iWork document as a Word, Excel, or PowerPoint file.Email your document as an iWork, Office, or PDF file from within iWork.Share your work on iWork.com, Apple&#039;s new document-sharing service, now available as a Public Beta. (Apple ID and email account required to publish documents and use the publisher link.)]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Software]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[12]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[79.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/e/199/iwork__83182_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[IWORK09]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[iLife 09]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/products/iLife-09.html]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Upgrade to iLife &amp;#8217;09 and get the most out of the photos, movies, and music on your Mac with the latest versions of iPhoto, iMovie, GarageBand, iWeb, and iDVD. Organize and search your photos by faces and places. Make a movie in minutes or edit with precision. Learn to play piano and guitar or record your own music. Create a stunning website and publish it anywhere.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Software]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2010-04-10]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[13]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[79.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:brand><![CDATA[Apple]]></g:brand>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://moluko.mybigcommerce.com/product_images/c/467/ilife__59335_zoom.jpg]]></g:image_link>
	<g:model_number><![CDATA[ILIFE09]]></g:model_number>
</entry>
</feed>